<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Ariel DeWinter</title><link>https://example.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Ariel DeWinter</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:56:33 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WP: Vacuum</title><link>https://example.com/blog/vacuum/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:56:33 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/vacuum/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;vacuum&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The noise was deafening. The whirrs, the clicks, the pops, the &lt;em&gt;roar&lt;/em&gt; of it all; Pepper sought refuge underneath the recliner as the beast came closer. It rarely ever went to areas that Pepper considered safe, though sometimes it intruded on her carefully-curated collections. A few minutes of tidying was a small price to pay for having to fight off the monster that appeared with such regularity.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Discord as a Tool for Brevity</title><link>https://example.com/blog/discord-as-a-tool-for-brevity/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2024 23:07:04 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/discord-as-a-tool-for-brevity/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://discord.com"&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;, love it or hate it, is the messaging app that&amp;rsquo;s used by folks all over the world for gaming groups, school groups, friend groups, and really any other kind of group that can communicate over text, voice, or screen-sharing. In the writing groups I&amp;rsquo;m in, it&amp;rsquo;s primarily used as a way to build community, share thoughts and ideas, and discuss snippets of work for encouragement or advice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="markdown-and-you"&gt;Markdown and You&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note that I said &amp;lsquo;&lt;em&gt;snippets&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rsquo;. For the vast majority of folks&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;, the largest message you can send in a chat is 2000 characters. Because Discord also uses &lt;a href="https://www.markdownguide.org/cheat-sheet/"&gt;the Markdown templating language&lt;/a&gt; (the same type of text &lt;a href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/arieldewinter/site/refs/heads/main/content/blog/discord-as-a-tool-for-brevity.md"&gt;this very post is (mostly) written in&lt;/a&gt;), the formatting is included in the text, so any additional formatting counts against the character count.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Scrivener and You</title><link>https://example.com/blog/scrivener-and-you/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 18:45:49 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/scrivener-and-you/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Stories take many forms: spoken word, written word, sung melody, campfire nostalgia, drunken retellings, plucked pain, solitary screams, incomprehensible babbling, the whispered chanting that echoes deep in your soul heralding the coming of Cthulhu, and even more that defy description.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Telling a story, on the surface, is simple: take the words out of your head and bring them into the world. With writing, the medium that we as writers use to bring the story into the world (oftentimes kicking and screaming) is the page. Now, what constitutes &amp;ldquo;the page&amp;rdquo; is up to interpretation: it could be an actual paper page that you write on, or it could be a computer screen that you type words on, or it could be a microphone that you dictate words to. What all those have in common is that they all eventually make your story accessible by people who aren&amp;rsquo;t you.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Masquerade</title><link>https://example.com/blog/masquerade/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 01:14:58 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/masquerade/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;masquerade&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If you don&amp;rsquo;t tell me why I should go, I will find something better to do with my time,&amp;rdquo; Shannon growled hotly in my ear. &amp;ldquo;Like&amp;hellip; you.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;&lt;em&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m&lt;/em&gt; not going to be here. I&amp;rsquo;m going to be at the party,&amp;rdquo; I retorted, trying to ignore the heat in my stomach. Hot goth girls make the best girlfriends, and it&amp;rsquo;s better when they&amp;rsquo;re annoyed at you. Might not be your cup of tea, but it works for me.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Tooth</title><link>https://example.com/blog/tooth/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 23:34:58 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/tooth/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;tooth&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Viola,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every time I see the wind run through the clothes on the line, it reminds me of you doing the same. They flip and somersault as if still on you. They double over in silent laughter, and I can see you doing the same. The silence is so loud I can almost hear it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every time I smell the petrichor outside, I think of your perfume decorating a room long after you&amp;rsquo;ve passed through. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why it reminds me of you, to be honest; I just know that it does. Perhaps it&amp;rsquo;s because the scent is fleeting, but always returns.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Lovely</title><link>https://example.com/blog/lovely/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 22:56:20 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/lovely/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;lovely&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Goodnight, darling,&amp;rdquo; I whispered as I tucked her in to bed. &amp;ldquo;Keep an eye out; the tooth fairy will come tonight and leave you some money!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Mommy&amp;hellip;,&amp;rdquo; the little voice whispered back, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m afwaid.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What are you afraid of, honey?&amp;rdquo; I patted the blanket as I knelt down by the bed. &amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;ve lost teeth before.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Ith thcary.&amp;rdquo; She held her blanket up to her face to leave only her beautiful brown eyes visible, so wide and full of insecurity about the world. How could I deny those eyes?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Mount</title><link>https://example.com/blog/mount/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2023 21:46:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/mount/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;mount&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If anyone has a stranglehold on that particular style of dress, it&amp;rsquo;s probably her.&amp;rdquo; The voice floated across the plaza, echoing against the chiseled stone columns of a different time. The chipped and scarred flagstones had seen much in their time, and they cared little for such trivialities as fashion; it changed so often throughout the millennia that it often appeared that the ghosts that walked upon them appeared blurred through different colors. &amp;ldquo;Who could wear straps like that? It&amp;rsquo;s scandalous, but somehow works for her.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Lazy</title><link>https://example.com/blog/lazy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 19:54:09 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/lazy/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;lazy&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soft clicking noises, low grunts, and the occasional hiss echoed through the room as the two women concentrated. Bella, a bead of sweat rolling slowly down her brow, concentrated as if her life depended on it; her fingers moved erratically, pressing and nudging seemingly without reason. Her lip curled as she sucked air through her teeth and grimaced.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Kim&amp;rsquo;s carefree smile only increased Bella&amp;rsquo;s building frustration. Though she struggled, Kim&amp;rsquo;s hands were aided by years of experience; she knew this dance inside and out. Curve by curve, edge by edge, she was on her home turf now. Nothing Bella did (or didn&amp;rsquo;t do) could throw her off her game now; she was in control.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Comfort</title><link>https://example.com/blog/comfort/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 19:58:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/comfort/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;comfort&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Jason, I neeeed you to understaaaaand how &lt;em&gt;fucking hot&lt;/em&gt; she is,&amp;rdquo; Bella slurred, trying (somewhat unsuccessfully) to stay on her stool. The latest hits of three years ago pumped over the bar speakers at barely-tolerable volumes, but Bella didn&amp;rsquo;t mind. &amp;ldquo;Like, gawd.&amp;rdquo; Standing up and planting her butt on the seat, she dropped her head on her folded arms. &amp;ldquo;Shmm nmmm wann ee wmm a rmm ike ee.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Pant, Pants, or Panting</title><link>https://example.com/blog/pant-pants-or-panting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 19:52:44 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/pant-pants-or-panting/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt words are &lt;strong&gt;pant, pants, or panting&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Have you ever seen worse handwriting in your life?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The crumpled note spread flat on the table refused to give up its secrets to the two auburn-haired heads staring at it in confusion. &amp;ldquo;Where did you find this again?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;In my pants after I picked them up from the dry cleaners.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re sure this is in English?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Yes, dummy. I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;s in English. Look: &amp;lsquo;miss our daily panting, coffee zoom&amp;rsquo;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Concrete</title><link>https://example.com/blog/concrete/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 19:50:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/concrete/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;concrete&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The temple was smaller than he thought it would be. Once-sharp steps, now crumbled with age, led upwards into darkness framed by roots and vines. A bird he didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize called out, and Ryan wondered for a fleeting second if the warning was for him or for those he came for. Machete in hand, he slowly moved forward, tromping through underbrush that had remained untouched for decades at least.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Safe</title><link>https://example.com/blog/safe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:43:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/safe/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;safe&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;There it is again. I always fucking cry.&lt;/em&gt; Those bastard tears, the betrayers; all Tanya wanted was to look in control, look like she had this all contained, look like this didn&amp;rsquo;t affect her that way.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The mirror, she knew, would not agree.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;What the &lt;em&gt;absolute fuck&lt;/em&gt; is wrong with you?&amp;rdquo;, she snarled, fighting the wetness she could already feel in her eyes. &amp;ldquo;Why do you think I would want to see her after all these years? I left for a &lt;em&gt;reason!&lt;/em&gt;&amp;rdquo; Her last words practically shouted, the other woman held up her hands.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Demand</title><link>https://example.com/blog/demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 19:41:13 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/demand/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;demand&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A.N. This is an excerpt from a &amp;ldquo;silly romance&amp;rdquo; story I published about a decade ago. Enjoy the silliness!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Elise stumbled to the edge of the dock, her tattered dress billowing in the storm. She cried out as the wind whipped around her and the waves climbed higher and higher, never ceasing their ominous crashes. Her delicate hand stretched as far as it could towards the lake &amp;ndash; the last place she had seen her love.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Truth</title><link>https://example.com/blog/truth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 19:39:39 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/truth/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;truth&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;If you look hard enough, you can see the patterns in the lights,&amp;rdquo; Stephanie gestured to the machine. &amp;ldquo;Okay, so let&amp;rsquo;s try it again. Pull back on the plunger, then let it slip through your fingers.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;He did as instructed, or at least tried; the ball flew from the plunger into the maze of lights and obstacles. It ricocheted around the cabinet, bouncing from bumper to spring to spinner. Steven tried frantically to stop the ball from escaping out the bottom, but grunted as it fell into the depths of the machine once more.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>WP: Heat</title><link>https://example.com/blog/heat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 18:52:47 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/heat/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is &lt;strong&gt;heat&lt;/strong&gt;!&lt;sup id="fnref:1"&gt;&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref"&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Tell me again.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Warehouse. At least thirty inside. Seriously Bart, this is reconnaissance, not a firefight. We&amp;rsquo;re quiet, we&amp;rsquo;re in, we&amp;rsquo;re out.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Did you at least bring any toys?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve always got more heat than you.&amp;rdquo; Jenna abandoned the conversation, instead creeping closer to one of the few windows of the large warehouse. She balanced one knee and slowly maneuvered a small mirror up to the bottom edge of the window, grimacing to herself while trying not to slip in the mud.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>