<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on Ariel DeWinter</title><link>https://example.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on Ariel DeWinter</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 19:54:09 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>WP: Lazy</title><link>https://example.com/blog/lazy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 19:54:09 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/lazy/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is lazy!1
Soft clicking noises, low grunts, and the occasional hiss echoed through the room as the two women concentrated. Bella, a bead of sweat rolling slowly down her brow, concentrated as if her life depended on it; her fingers moved erratically, pressing and nudging seemingly without reason. Her lip curled as she sucked air through her teeth and grimaced.
Kim&amp;rsquo;s carefree smile only increased Bella&amp;rsquo;s building frustration.</description></item><item><title>WP: Comfort</title><link>https://example.com/blog/comfort/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 19:58:28 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/comfort/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is comfort!1
&amp;ldquo;Jason, I neeeed you to understaaaaand how fucking hot she is,&amp;rdquo; Bella slurred, trying (somewhat unsuccessfully) to stay on her stool. The latest hits of three years ago pumped over the bar speakers at barely-tolerable volumes, but Bella didn&amp;rsquo;t mind. &amp;ldquo;Like, gawd.&amp;rdquo; Standing up and planting her butt on the seat, she dropped her head on her folded arms. &amp;ldquo;Shmm nmmm wann ee wmm a rmm ike ee.</description></item><item><title>WP: Pant, Pants, or Panting</title><link>https://example.com/blog/pant-pants-or-panting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 19:52:44 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/pant-pants-or-panting/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt words are pant, pants, or panting!1
&amp;ldquo;Have you ever seen worse handwriting in your life?&amp;rdquo;
The crumpled note spread flat on the table refused to give up its secrets to the two auburn-haired heads staring at it in confusion. &amp;ldquo;Where did you find this again?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;In my pants after I picked them up from the dry cleaners.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;You&amp;rsquo;re sure this is in English?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Yes, dummy. I&amp;rsquo;m sure it&amp;rsquo;s in English.</description></item><item><title>WP: Concrete</title><link>https://example.com/blog/concrete/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 19:50:10 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/concrete/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is concrete!1
The temple was smaller than he thought it would be. Once-sharp steps, now crumbled with age, led upwards into darkness framed by roots and vines. A bird he didn&amp;rsquo;t recognize called out, and Ryan wondered for a fleeting second if the warning was for him or for those he came for. Machete in hand, he slowly moved forward, tromping through underbrush that had remained untouched for decades at least.</description></item><item><title>WP: Safe</title><link>https://example.com/blog/safe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 19:43:05 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/safe/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is safe!1
There it is again. I always fucking cry. Those bastard tears, the betrayers; all Tanya wanted was to look in control, look like she had this all contained, look like this didn&amp;rsquo;t affect her that way.
The mirror, she knew, would not agree.
&amp;ldquo;What the absolute fuck is wrong with you?&amp;rdquo;, she snarled, fighting the wetness she could already feel in her eyes. &amp;ldquo;Why do you think I would want to see her after all these years?</description></item><item><title>WP: Demand</title><link>https://example.com/blog/demand/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 19:41:13 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/demand/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is demand!1
A.N. This is an excerpt from a &amp;ldquo;silly romance&amp;rdquo; story I published about a decade ago. Enjoy the silliness!
Elise stumbled to the edge of the dock, her tattered dress billowing in the storm. She cried out as the wind whipped around her and the waves climbed higher and higher, never ceasing their ominous crashes. Her delicate hand stretched as far as it could towards the lake &amp;ndash; the last place she had seen her love.</description></item><item><title>WP: Truth</title><link>https://example.com/blog/truth/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2023 19:39:39 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/truth/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is truth!1
&amp;ldquo;If you look hard enough, you can see the patterns in the lights,&amp;rdquo; Stephanie gestured to the machine. &amp;ldquo;Okay, so let&amp;rsquo;s try it again. Pull back on the plunger, then let it slip through your fingers.&amp;rdquo;
He did as instructed, or at least tried; the ball flew from the plunger into the maze of lights and obstacles. It ricocheted around the cabinet, bouncing from bumper to spring to spinner.</description></item><item><title>WP: Heat</title><link>https://example.com/blog/heat/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2023 18:52:47 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/blog/heat/</guid><description>Today&amp;rsquo;s prompt word is heat!1
&amp;ldquo;Tell me again.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Warehouse. At least thirty inside. Seriously Bart, this is reconnaissance, not a firefight. We&amp;rsquo;re quiet, we&amp;rsquo;re in, we&amp;rsquo;re out.&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;Did you at least bring any toys?&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;ve always got more heat than you.&amp;rdquo; Jenna abandoned the conversation, instead creeping closer to one of the few windows of the large warehouse. She balanced one knee and slowly maneuvered a small mirror up to the bottom edge of the window, grimacing to herself while trying not to slip in the mud.</description></item></channel></rss>